mobilebytes.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy | MobileBytes | Restaurant POS for iPad

LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 11, 2014

We at Mobile Bytes, LLC (d/b/a MobileBytes) (“MobileBytes,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) value the privacy of our customers and partners. The following privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”), as modified from time to time, describes our practices in connection with information collected through our www.mobilebytes.com website (the “Site”), our MobileBytes mobile applications, any other linked pages, features, content, mobile applications, and any other services we offer from time to time in connection with any of the foregoing (collectively, the “Suite”).

By visiting or using the Suite, you agree to the practices and policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Suite. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Suite following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

## Information We Collect

We collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Suite – personal information and non-personal information. “Personal information” is any information that can individually identify you and includes (without limitation) your name, email address, telephone number, fax number, postal address, credit card, debit card, and billing and contact information. “Non-personal information” includes information that does not personally identify you, but may include (without limitation) tracking and usage information about your location, demographics, transaction information, use of the Suite and the Internet.

## Personal Information

There are a number of circumstances in which you may voluntarily supply us with your personal information. The following lists the most common ways in which we may collect your personal information:

  * Registration for an account with the Suite
  * Purchase and use of services from the Suite
  * Sign up to receive email newsletters from us
  * Requests for customer service or other assistance
  * Participation in surveys, special events, and promotions
  * Participation on social media accounts involving MobileBytes and our products
  * Participation in our blog, communities, chat rooms, and other interactive services
  * Any other place within the Suite where you knowingly volunteer personal information

## Social Media Sites

When you interact with any MobileBytes account on a social media platform, such as Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, Pinterest, or Instagram, we may collect the personal information that you make available to us on that page or account, including your user ID and/or user name, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. Please note, however, that we will comply with the privacy policies of the corresponding social media platform and we will only collect and store such personal information that we are permitted to collect by these social media platforms.

## Non-Personal Information

When you interact with the Suite, our servers may keep an activity log that does not identify you individually. Generally, we collect and store the following categories of non-personal information:

  * Demographic data of Suite users, including end customers.
  * Transaction information such as purchases and use of discounts/rewards of both Suite users and end customers.
  * Device information about your computer, mobile device, or other device that you use to access the Suite, which may include your IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language, and other transactional information.
  * Usage information about your use of the Suite, such as a reading history of the pages you view.
  * Additional traffic data, such as time and date of access, software crash reports, session identification number, access times, and referring website addresses.
  * Your search terms and search results.
  * Other information regarding our users’ use of the Suite.

## Use of Cookies

When you interact with the Suite, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested.

Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. We may use these technologies to also collect and store information about your usage of the Suite, such as the pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen.

We work with third party advertising companies who may also utilize flash or enhanced cookies or web beacons to better provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. As a result, we may also deliver a file to you through the Suite (known as a “web beacon”) from an advertising network partner. Web beacons allow advertising networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. These beacons may, for example, log that you have viewed a certain product on our Suite, and then show you an ad for similar products when you browse to another website. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

These third party advertising partners do not use this technology to collect personal information about you, or have access to any personal information you have provided to us. They may, however, anonymously track your internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond the Suite. We do not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, and to opt out of such ad networks’ and services’ advertising practices, please visit the National Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features, content, or personalization available through the Suite.

## 'Do Not Track' Practices

At this time, we do not honor do-not-track signals from browsers or other consumer choice mechanisms regarding the collection of behavioral tracking data. While we collect personal information from you as described above, we do not collect personal information from you to monitor your online activities across third party websites or online services and over time (also known as behavioral advertising or interest-based advertising). We do not use or allow third parties to collect personal information from you in the Suite in order to monitor your online activities across third party websites or online services and over time.

## Email and Other Communications

We may contact you by email or other means. For example, we may send you promotional offers or our newsletter. If you do not want to receive email from us, please let us know through the “unsubscribe” feature included in our communications.

## Our Use of Information

We use the information we collect from you and about you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience with the Suite.

We may use the information we collect from and about you in the following ways:

  * Provide you with the products and services you request from us
  * Post your user generated content to our Suite as you request
  * Communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information about features on our Suite
  * Communicate with you about changes to our policies
  * Personalize content and experiences on our Suite
  * Send you newsletters, offers, and promotions for our products and services, third party products and services, or special events by email or other media
  * Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests, including advertising based on your activity on our Suite or activity on third party sites and applications
  * Administer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys
  * Optimize or improve our products, services, and operations
  * Perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Suite and their purchasing patterns

## Our Disclosure of Information

We do not and will not sell your personal information to any third party outside of MobileBytes, and will only share personal information as provided below and within our company.

## Service Providers

We may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents, or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the services offered on our Suite, such as hosting, billing, payment processing, marketing, analytics, customer service, fraud protection, etc. We may need to share your personal information with them, but we require that all of our service providers keep personal information confidential and not disclose it to third parties and not use it for any other purpose.

## Emergency Situations

We may also use or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Suite; (b) respond to requests from public and government authorities; (c) protect and defend our rights or property, the Suite, or our users; and (d) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Suite or the public.

## Merger or Sale

If we sell all or part of our business or make a sale or transfer of our assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of our business, MobileBytes may transfer your information to the party or parties involved as part of that transaction.

We may share your non-personal information, in aggregated form, with certain third parties, such as restaurant associations, reporting agencies, and industry vendors.

## Security

We are concerned about ensuring the security of your personal information. We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personal information collected through the Suite from access, loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction by any unauthorized party. Please understand, however, that no transmission of data over the internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

## Children’s Online Privacy

MobileBytes respects the privacy of children and we are committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not knowingly collect, solicit, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Suite or send any information about yourself to us. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided personal information to us without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information immediately.

We remind and encourage all parents to check and monitor their children’s online activities. Parents have the right to review and have deleted any personal information we may have inadvertently collected from their children, and refuse to permit further collection of that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@mobilebytes.com.

## User Access and Control

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided to us, you may contact us directly at support@mobilebytes.com. In your request, please specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of MobileBytes to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes, if any. To make such a request, please send an email to support@mobilebytes.com, with “California Privacy Rights Request” in the subject line. You must include sufficient detail for us to locate your file; at a minimum, your name, email and postal address.

## Links To or From Other Sites

Please note that the Suite may link to other websites and online services operated by third parties. These websites and applications operate independently from us, and we do not control their privacy policies, which may be different from ours. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party websites or applications.

## Notice to Non-US Users

If you are located outside of the United States of America, please be aware that your personal information will be transferred to the United States of America, the laws of which may be deemed by your country to have inadequate data protection. If you are located outside of the United States of America and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion without specific notice to you. Please look at the effective date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Service after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy will indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

## Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, please contact:

  * Webmaster
  * Mobile Bytes, LLC
  * 130 N Central Ave Suite 301
  * Phoenix, AZ, USA 85004
  * 480.351.8800
